<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/">
  <channel>
    <title>News</title>
    <description>Updates and Announcements</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:43:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>WesterosCraft Forums</generator>
    <link>https://forum.westeroscraft.com/</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"
      href="https://forum.westeroscraft.com/forum/news.2/index.rss" />
    <item>
      <title>Gathering anonymous feedback on the server!</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 15:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>https://forum.westeroscraft.com/threads/gathering-anonymous-feedback-on-the-server.4027/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4027</guid>
      <author>invalid@example.com (geeberry)</author>
      <category domain="https://forum.westeroscraft.com/forum/news.2/"><![CDATA[News]]></category>
      <dc:creator>geeberry</dc:creator>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="bbWrapper">Howdy everyone!<br />
<br />
Hope your spring is going great so far. Behind the scenes, I've been working on improving our project management (along with lots of other exciting things like a plot system, new WorldMachine terrain, and more!). To further those plans, <b>I am looking to gather some feedback, suggestions, ideas, or comments about the operation of the server.</b>  I've made a feedback form where I can solicit some of these responses and ideally influence the future of the project.<br />
<br />
I'm looking for general feedback on what you think is working for the project, what you believe isn't working, and any ideas to improve. I am open to any other thoughts from both current and former community members, outside observers and anyone else. <b>You can remain anonymous!  The form is only viewable by me, not the mods. </b> There is a username field so you can identify yourself, but only if you wish.  Alternatively, if you wish to directly DM me on Discord, please do, always down to chat! <br />
<br />
The form is here: <a href="https://forms.gle/WoBKjs5cxJ2ZjebT6" target="_blank" class="link link--external" rel="noopener">https://forms.gle/WoBKjs5cxJ2ZjebT6</a> <br />
<br />
Thank you everyone, looking forward to seeing the feedback</div>]]></content:encoded>
      <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>